Jinwoo...
You know you've changed. a lot.
And then there's me who
hasn't really changed at all.
Well. everyone's different.
I changed a lot because
a lot's happened.
Yeah. very true.
There's one thing I can
finally admit. though.
I'm too timid for this job.
I had hoped I'd overcome that. but...
I just couldn't.
I should've been signing up
for A and B-Rank dungeons.
or if not those. then maybe
at least some C-Rank ones.
I knew that. but I purposely
stuck with the D and E-ranks.
Those low-ranked raids
were how I met you. though.
and how I found myself
healing you over and over again.
At first. I was a little annoyed
by how often you got hurt.
Yet somehow you always survived.
You got back up and kept fighting.
That passionate fire in your
eyes never flickered out.
In fact. it's burned in my mind.
We promised that we would
go out to eat somewhere.
But. you should have this back.
Hm... can I know why?
'Cause I'm leaving.
I'm retiring as a hunter.
Yeah. I'm moving back home.
So give me a heads up if you're ever
in the area and I'll show you around.
For old times'.
Fair enough. When that happens.
I'll cash in our rain check.
Sure.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Frankly. I don't see an E-Rank like
you having a hand in Taeshik's defeat.
I was the one who tested you for
a potential reawakening. after all.
But I do feel compelled
to give you a warning.
If you want to live
a long life. then be careful.
What do you mean?
You survived when Dongsuk Hwang's
strike team was wiped out too.
You and that D-Rank may have
painted targets on your backs.
Because it just so happens that
Dongsuk's brother is Dongsoo Hwang.
If he isn't after you two.
I would be shocked.
You mean Dongsoo Hwang
as in the S-Rank?
-For real?
-Yes.
What actually happened
doesn't matter to him.
His only takeaway
is that his brother died.
while you and some other
low-rank made it out alive.
S-Ranks aren't bound by laws.
With that much power
at their fingertips.
they can choose to bring about
miracles. or absolute destruction.
So one of the monsters that even monsters
fear is out for your blood. Jinwoo Sung.
hence my warning.
If possible.
I suggest you take your family and
leave the country as soon as you can.
One more reason
I need to get stronger.
I have to.
Otherwise...
I won't be able to survive.
Uh. Jinho?
Just one question.
what am I looking at here?
I thought it was obvious.
like what else could it be?
This is our strike team!
When making my selections. I prioritized
people who are registered hunters
but have reasons they can't work and
people who are having trouble getting by.
The injured and drunk made the cut?
It really works better for us.
so yeah!
Can't raid C-Rank gates without
eight people. and these want the cash.
Hm?
Bro. is that a kid?
Minors can raid as long
as they've awakened.
And she has. so it's okay.
'Scuse me.
-Huh?
That's kind of rude.
I'm a qualified hunter. not a kid.
You're in high school. though. right?
You raided before?
Well. n-no.
I'm guessing you're E-Rank?
What's it matter what rank I am?
Touche. It doesn't matter
since you're staying here.
Jinho and I will be the only
ones who go through the gate.
So. you two really wanna
clear this thing by yourselves?
While the rest of us get three million
big ones just for sitting around?
Right. that's three million
for every raid.
Not half bad since you aren't
required to fight. huh?
Catch is. you can't talk about it.
If you go public with our deal.
per the contract.
you'll have to pay us back
ten times what we paid you.
This is the Stealth stone I
got from beating Taeshik Kang.
Might as well use it now.
Nice. looks like it worked.
You ready. boss?
What are you wearing?
This is a full suit of buff-boosting
armor. special-ordered from Italy.
S'a little something I had prepared
once you agreed to raid with me.
And now I'm ready
for whatever trials await!
Not to me mean but you better
take that off before I rip it off.
Okay.
Boss. would you mind helping me up?
Onward!
Gotta admit I'm nervous. though.
Dude. I swear to...
what did I just say?
At least let me keep the helmet!
Fine. whatever.
-Let's go.
-Right!
Should we let them raid it alone?
It feels sorta wrong.
I mean. we warned them and they paid in
advance. so whatever happens happens.
All I know is a C-Rank dungeon isn't
gonna be cleared by a D and an E-Rank.
Those two greenhorns don't have a
damn clue what they're getting into.
Song-yi must be skipping class today.
How long's it been?
I'd say about an hour now?
But it would take a normal squad at
least two hours to clear. so get comfy.
I guess they ran away.
they're lucky to be alive.
I don't think they're leaving
because they're giving up!
Look. the gate's closing!
No. they beat the boss?
-Where's the next gate?
-About an hour from here.
All right. let's get goin'.
We're moving. everyone!
Got two more dungeons to clear!
Ah...
or would you rather leave the other six
million you could earn today on the table?
Are they for real?
Who are these guys?
Hey. I'm done mining all
of the mana crystals over here!
Sounds good.
I had better wrap this up. too.
I'm heading out.
Dude. more work today?
Yep. Don't forget to lock up.
Has he had that skill
this whole time?
Or did he get stronger?
Gotta say. It wasn't fun
earning the stealth skill.
But. man. is it useful.
Fighting's easy when your
opponent can't see you.
Oh. the Dash skill
leveled up. that's cool.
And with my new Advanced
Dagger-Wielding and Fatal Strike skills...
I feel unstoppable!
Awesome job today!
As soon as I snag all the goods
we can be on our way.
You should rest up in the meantime.
Thanks. will do.
My new skills are handy.
Though they'd be a lot handier if I
had the mana to use them longer.
I'll have to put more ability points toward
increasing my intellect going forward.
Should I take this momentum
all the way to the Demon Castle?
No.
I probably fall somewhere
between B and A-Rank as I am now.
I could try taking on
that dungeon. but I dunno.
Wasn't aware there was a target
level I was supposed to be aiming for.
A "job-change quest?"
Manager Ahn!
Look at this!
Whatcha got. Kichul?
A few recent bids for the local
C-Rank dungeon gates.
One hundred fifty million?
Who in their right mind blows that much
money on the permit for a C-Rank gate once
let alone multiple times?
There's a strike team
that's spending nearly
double the market rate
for C-Rank gates around here.
leaving nothing for our guild's
lower-rank hunters.
Who are they?
Never heard of this squad or this
"Jinho Yoo" character that's leading them.
He's the son of Yoojin
Construction's president.
The Yoojin Construction?
Spending like this will
just put them in the red.
Seems excessive for
a rich kid playing hunter.
E-Rank. Jinwoo Sung?
Yes. sir. They threw together
a band of misfits and randos.
It's hard to say
what they're planning.
Is this the same Jinwoo Sung
from the double dungeon incident?
There's something here.
I can smell it.
-You gonna go?
-I'm thinking.
Hey. sorry we're late!
-Huh?
Well. you won't hear me complain.
Besides. you're actually
ahead of schedule.
It took a sec to collect all those crystals.
so I thought we were pressed for time.
But. onto the next!
Man. you've gotta be dead tired.
Want me to drive?
It'd be nice to have
something to do. if it's cool.
Oh. I gotcha...
What?
Nothing.
Sir. you think
Jinwoo Sung reawakened?
That is what I just said.
Anything to base that on?
There have been three huge
disasters recently
that Hunter Sung survived
despite the casualties.
First. the double dungeon.
Second. the annihilation
of Dongsuk Hwang's strike team.
and last but certainly not least. getting
caught in Taeshik Kang's murder spree.
There was just a handful
of survivors for each incident.
and Sung was always among them.
A reawakening is the only
explanation that would make sense.
Well. I guess that's true.
So where are you headed now.
Manager Ahn? To research?
No. Kichul.
There's a promising rookie
out there I'd like to go scout.
There's a plot twist.
What is this. a picnic?
Hi.
And bye. This place
is a restricted area.
Sorry about that.
but we noticed there were
a bunch of hunters hanging out over here.
and couldn't help but take a closer look.
That blue light is a gate. yeah?
Is it okay for you to be this close?
I'm not a kid so stop treating me like
one. You can treat me like a hunter.
Wait. if you're a hunter. then. are you
on the strike team in charge of this gate?
-Yes.
-Uh...
But...
Ha ha. gotcha!
Hunter Sung must be clearing
the dungeon alone as we speak!
If I'm right about this guy.
he could be a big find!
No. bigger than big!
I see. sorry for disturbing you.
You be careful. little lady.
Sir. are we really leaving now?
The captain's back!
Get ready to move out. guys.
Hey. do you have any raids
scheduled for tomorrow?
I remembered there's something
I gotta go do. so can I take off?
Hm. Let's see what I've got here.
Yeah. I reserved a couple.
Want me to cancel?
And waste money?
I know you have it. but still.
I can hold onto them
for another two days.
Okay. in that case. why don't
we go ahead and delay.
Consider them delayed.
I'm sorry about the wait.
c'mon. let's get moving!
That same dream. again.
It's almost time.
See ya later. boss!
Hm?
I apologize if this is sudden.
Hunter Sung.
The name's Sangmin Ahn and
I'm currently the manager
of the Second Administration
Team for the White Tiger Guild.
If you have just a moment to spare.
I'd love to have a word with you.
I'm sure my guild's
reputation precedes itself.
But White Tiger isn't just a great guild.
it's one of the country's best.
And we're always on the lookout
for promising new talent
to help us climb even higher.
Since I know your time
is precious. I'll be direct.
I recognize you're a capable hunter
and I'd like you to join our guild.
We'll pay double what
Yoojin Construction does.
And if you have any
additional conditions.
just let me know and I'm sure
we can arrange to see them met.
How's that?
For someone who was E-Rank a few
short months ago. this is quite the bargain!
He's bound to say yes!
What's White Tiger HQ valued at?
You know off the top of your head?
Oh. uh. I'd say it's probably appraised
somewhere around fifty billion or so?
Interesting. then your
entire HQ is the offer?
I'm not sure I'm following you here.
Hm?
What? Thirty billion?
-Why'd he freak out?
-Who knows?
That's the value of the
building I was promised
by Yoojin Construction.
and it keeps going higher.
You said you'd double that.
which is why I figured
a building worth
fifty billion would do.
If you think I'm bluffing.
I've got the proof right here.
W-well. uh. thing is. uh. negotiating
that kind of money is above my pay grade.
I'm sure once I discuss it
with the brass. though...
No need. I believe we're done here.
Huh?
I was too desperate.
I should've looked into his deal
with Yoojin Construction first!
Before I go.
I'm curious how you
found out about me.
It's not because you've been
snooping around. is it?
Where'd he?
Wait. does he have the Stealth skill?
Suddenly that outrageous
offer makes sense!
A reawakened with Stealth
is worth a whole building!
Maybe two!
Sorry. I meant no harm
in researching you.
But. I wouldn't call it
"snooping" per se.
Don't turn around.
There's been a shortage of C-Rank gates.
which has put a stopper on our training.
Our policy is to only send
rookies on raids they can handle.
And so. I was tasked with investigating
who was buying up all of the gates.
when I came across your name.
Hunter Sung.
Apart from yourself. Mister Ahn.
just how many people know about me?
It's only me and one
of my subordinates.
I see. I'd rather
keep a low profile.
If word should get out about me. you
two will be the first people I suspect.
Well. I'm here on
official guild business
so I'm supposed to make
a report to our president.
But I really don't wanna die so. I'll see
to it that we both keep our mouths shut.
I appreciate that.
I never stopped to think monopolizing
the gates would cause trouble.
My turn to say sorry now.
because we are going to continue.
That's a real shame. then.
Our developing hunters are trapped
in a bottleneck without those gates.
Well. we could make a deal.
You would do that?
What's the catch here?
Three of our C-Rank gates can be
claimed by your guild if the price is right.
You won't be raiding C-Rank dungeons
anytime soon if you let this offer slide.
It's like the
home shopping channel. but...
I understand.
how much are you asking?
I want three hundred million apiece.
You... you're joking!
Most we could profit
from C-Rank mana crystals
and essence stones is about two
hundred million and that's on a good day!
If you could lower the price to two
hundred million at least. then I would--
Works for me.
Seems we have ourselves a deal.
Oh... we do.
Which means we'll be taking
three gates off your hands.
Right.
Three gates for a total
of six hundred million.
Okay. deal.
Wire the money here
by the end of the day.
And one last thing. a parting gift.
Close your eyes and open
your mouth. please.
Huh?
I assure you this gift
isn't going to hurt you.
Did my cut just heal?
See ya.
Since you showed me your
stealth and recovery skills.
can I take that as a sign you trust me. or
is that simply wishful thinking on my part?
If you don't go blab my secret.
then yes. Mister Ahn. I'll trust you.
So. how'd it go?
Were you able to scout
a new White Tiger?
No. but. Kichul.
I think that guy is a jackpot bigger
than either of us could ever imagine.
Boss. I confirmed the transfer.
The six hundred mil is really there.
How'd you sell those gates so high?
And right before
we canceled them. too!
Who bought them from you?
Let's call it a trade secret.
What?
There's a ton of C-Rank gates
in our area now?
Uh. yes.
Yoojin Construction only bought
the three we purchased from them!
And the rest are all selling
for seventy million or less.
so it seems Hunter Sung
totally tricked you. sir!
Not only did I fail to recruit
the guy. I let him con me!
What a nightmare!
Guess strength gives people
courage to pull anything!
A message? Am I fired?
This is Jinwoo Sung.
with this. we're even.
I'll forget the fact
that you spied on me.
Oh. okay. Sung.
that's how it is. huh?
Money-wise. you did win.
but at least I earned your trust.
Tricky as you are.
You saying Hunter Sung
sent that message just now?
Yeah.
Though he raked me over the coals.
He gave me his contact info
in the process.
For the time being. I think
I can be satisfied with that.
So a job-change quest.
Well. should be interesting.
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app